<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Cube World Basics</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_websearch">Web search</string>
    <string name="app_not_available">Sorry, there\'s no web browser available</string>
    
    <string name="home_about">Cube World is a 3D action RPG for PC made by Wollay and his wife. It was released in July 2013, and is still under continued development. It is currently available for purchase at $20. Gameplay is inspired by well-established games of similar genres, like Diablo and Minecraft, aiming to combine the best aspects of randomly-generated content, exploration, combat, and customization.</string>
    <string name="biomes_about">Landscapes are geographical environments in Cube World.\nEach landscape has its unique climate and theme as well as contain unique flora and fauna. Currently a world can consist of six different landscapes. Four additional landscapes are due for future updates of the game.</string>
    <string name="classes_about">Classes determine the main abilities and traits of your Cube World character. Along with specializations, they are your characters main distinguishing factor.</string>
    <string name="controls_about">Gameplay begins by creating a character of your choosing. This involves selecting from a variety of customizations, including race, cosmetics and your class. Afterward, you must select which world you wish to adventure into; these worlds are randomly-generated based on an initial seed. Once you have been dropped into your world with your chosen character, you are free to explore with climbing, sailing and hanggliding. Your character gains new abilities by gaining experience and progressing in levels; this is done through combat and daily mission completion. Your character also gains new items which can further increase the power of your character. Some items can be equipped, others are consumable such as foods and potions, and some can be used in crafting to create even better items. Your character can also tame and collect pets, which will assist you in combat.</string>
    <string name="equipment_about">Equipment is a name for items that can be equipped into the main equipment slots. Equipment can have different Rarity levels. Equipment includes weapons, armor and amulets. Armor and weapons can also change your character\'s appearance when equipped.</string>
    <string name="crafting_about">Crafting is the method used in Cube World to create Items such as armor and weapons through the use of materials and formulas.\nIn order to craft different items, the player can use the crafting menu (C key), though certain items can only be crafted while the player is standing near specific crafting props (Fires, Spinning Wheels, Anvils, Workbenches, and Saws are examples). Each class (Warrior, Ranger, Spirit Mage and Rogue) can only craft Armour and Weapons available to that class. The crafting categories are Weapon Crafting, Armor Crafting, Jewel Crafting, Cooking and Alchemy.</string>
    <string name="items_about">Items can be obtained from Mobs, Missions, NPCs. Apart from that, items are also craft-able.</string>
    <string name="monsters_about"></string>
    <string name="pets_about">Pets are friendly mobs whose primary purpose is to defend the character they\'re accompanying. They are equippable, as is the case with most items.</string>
    <string name="races_about">There are currently three subtypes of Races in Cube World. All three types are humanoid. They are playable, neutral and hostile. The playable races you can choose in Cube World determines your character\'s physical appearance. As of the alpha, none of the races currently have any specific traits or perks.\nThere are also nine playable races in Cube World, these races also appear in-game as friendly NPCs and hostile Mobs.</string>
    <string name="world_about">A main feature of Cube World is the random world generation. In contrast to many games, worlds are not designed by a level designer, but procedurally generated by the game using equations and random numbers. The result is an infinite world.</string>
    
    <string-array name="menu_items_array">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Classes</item>
        <item>Controls</item>
        <item>Crafting</item>
        <item>Equipment</item>
        <item>Items</item>
        <item>Monsters</item>
        <item>Pets</item>
        <item>Races</item>
        <item>World</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
